Rubinow, Isaac Max Papers 5616
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Commons, John R., 1913-1917 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  correspondence with Rubinow re attitude of Federal Commission on Industrial Relations on social insurance - asks Rubinow for ideas (12/1913); letter to Rubinow re locating position for him on a state commission for social insurance, (2/19/17)
- Commonwealth College, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  Rubinow as member of Commonwealth Advisory Committee, routine business correspondence; re investigation into un-American and Communistic activities of Commonwealth
- Community Chest of Cincinnati and Hamilton County, 1931-1936 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Congressmen, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  correspondence from Rubinow requesting copies of various bills they introduced
- Consumer's League (Cincinnati), 1931-1936 (Box 2, Folder 65-67)
  Includes minutes, Cincinnati Consumer's League; correspondence re Rubinow's involvement as a member of Board of Director's; routine correspondence dealing with activities of the organization
- Council of Social Agencies of Cincinnati, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  correspondence re routine speaking engagements
- Cr, 1914-1935 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Cronback, Abraham - Professor, Hebrew Union College, 1931-1936 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  re lecture engagements; fund raising project for American Friends Service Committee; routine literary correspondence
- Cu, 1910-1935 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  routine literary correspondence with Current History, Curtis Publishing Company; personal correspondence
- Da, 1928-1935 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  notes of congratulations re Rubinow's election as President of National Conference of Jewish Social Service; correspondence with YMCA, Dayton, Ohio re series of lectures and routine
- Davis, M.M., 1914-1935 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  significant amount of correspondence with Davis, Executive Secretary, Committee on Dispensary Development, United Hospital Fund and Director (later) of Julius Rosenwald Fund re medical services; social insurance
- Davis, M.M., 1913-1924 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  routine correspondence with Dawson, Actuary Consultant
- De, 1911-1936 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Correspondence with Frederic Dewhurst, Committee on Social Security of the Social Science Research Council, re Lundeen Bill
- DeHaas, Jacob - Chairman, Jabotinsky Reception Committee, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 4a)
  Rubinow did not want to be identified with Jabotinsky in the U.S. because of differing political views
- Devine, Edward - Charity Org. Society (NYC), Secretary, also special representative, American Red Cross, 1912-1917 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  re literary correspondence; lectures by Rubinow at New York School of Philanthropy of which Devine was Director
- Dewey, Davis R-- Dewey, Admiral, U.S. Navy Department and Secretary, American Statistical Association, 1905-1918 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Di, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  correspondence with Courtenay Dinwiddle, Secretary, National Child Labor Committee re speaking engagement re minimum wage laws; single issue of "Digest of Events of Jewish Interest," published by Jewish Statistical Bureau
- Do - W.F. Dodd, Legislative Reference Bureau (111.), 1917-1936 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  re heal insurance; Dodd, Yale University School of Law re workmen's compensation laws investigation; personal correspondence and routine
- Douglas, Paul H., 1928-1936 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  correspondence re cooperation between John B. Andrews, Epstein, Rubinow and Douglas re Ohio Plan for social insurance, re U.S. political situation; re German problem; re disagreements between Andrews and Rubinow; re literary correspondence, "Quest for Security,"; and re Frances Perkins, no invitation to Rubinow for unemployment conference
- Downey, E.H., 1915-1920 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  letter of recommendation for Rubinow from Downey for position as statistician with Liberty Mutual Insurance; discussion of other job possibilities for Rubinow; discussion of disability cases under Wisconsin Workmen's Compensation Act
- Du-Dy, 1914-1934 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Ea, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  letter to Crystal Eastman (London) re future of social insurance in the U.S.
- Ec - Olga S. Halsey, Committee on Economic Security, 1932-1934 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  re insurance for chronic illness and routine
- Ed, 1914-1933 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Correspondence with Charles Edgerton, Cornell University Professor of Law re personal and re Lawrence Strike (3/3/22): law and order brutality and routine
- El, 1934-1936 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Ellis and Company, 1930-1936 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  re routine, personal, financial matters
- Em, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  correspondence with Henry C. Emery, Yale University Professor re literary
- En-Ez, 1928-1934 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Encyclopedia of Social Sciences, 1928-1934 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
- England (Box 3, Folder 21)
  routine literary correspondence with "Town and Country Review," n.d.
- Epstein, Abraham - Research Director, Pennsylvania Old Age Commission, 1924-1926 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  correspondence re dependent aged in California; old age legislation; social matters
- Epstein, Abraham - National Old Age Pension League, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  re organizing activities of the League; problems with fund raising for American Association for Old Age Security; routine literary correspondence re Epstein's mss. from Rubinow re old age pension amendment killed in Pennsylvania
- Epstein, Abraham, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  re arrangement of conferences; foreign social insurance; financial support for AALL; discusses cooperation with John B. Andrews and the AALL
- Epstein, Abraham, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Epstein, Abraham, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  re competition with the Eagles organization salary for Mr. Herbert Bigelow (Executive Committee member of American Association for Old Age Security)
- Epstein, Abraham, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  disagreement between Epstein and Rubinow re Ohio Unemployment Insurance Bill and routine
- Epstein, Abraham, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  re Andrew's criticism of Epstein in AALL Review; re unemployment insurance legislation; re correspondence with Professor Joseph Chamberlain (Columbia) on difference of opinion on unemployment insurance; copy of Andrews letter to N.I. stone re legislation; routine literary correspondence
- Epstein, Abraham, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
  letter to Rubinow re events in Washington, mentions Bakke, Frances Perkins, Elizabeth Brandeis, Mary VanKleek and others; William Green mentioned in letter (10/12/3*+) re article by Green attacking workers contributions; letters re Epstein's illness; re Ohio's old age insurance plan; disagreements with Frances Perkins re insurance plans and conferences; Susan Brandeis1 debate with Epstein and attack by her re Wisconsin vs. Ohio Plan (unemployment); routine literary correspondence
- Epstein, Abraham, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  Substantive amount of correspondence re Social Security Bill between Rubinow and Epstein outlining their differences of opinion and comparing it with similar foreign plans
- Epstein, Moses P., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Mrs. Moses P. Epstein with Hadassah requesting early reports and correspondence re Hadassah Medical Association
- Fa, 1926-1936 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Fe, 1911-1936 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  letter from William B. Feakins (Forum Lecture Bureau) requesting Rubinow to arrange a lecture on topic of interest to a woman's club in Newark, NJ (l91l); also (1928) re connecting himself with Transcontinental Lecture Tours of which Feakins was President; routine
- Federal Emergency Relief Administration (Box 3, Folder 35)
  routine, n.d.
- Federal Employment, 1913-1918 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  routine correspondence during Rubinow's employment with Federal Trade Commission working on Grain-Resumption of Employment and other government related routine correspondence
- Federated Jewish Charities of Boston, 1923-1927 (Box 3, Folder 37-39)
  Correspondence with Maurice B. Hexter, Executive Director re routine literary correspondence and statistical data on various subjects
- Feldman, Herman - Professor of Industrial Relations, Dartmouth College, 1934-1937 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  re setting up meeting with Epstein, Gray, Rubinow and Feldman to discuss differences; lengthy letters re various sections of social insurance bills
- Fi, 1908-1936 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  routine literary correspondence; personal
- Field, Jacob, 1924-1935 (Box 3, Folder 42-43)
  re letters of recommendation for Field for various positions; personal correspondence
- Fl, 1923-1928 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  correspondence with Bernard Flexner, President, Palestine Economic Corporation, re agreement between American Jewish Physicians Committee and Governing Board of the Hadassah Hospitals in Palestine; substantive data on financial status of Hadassah Medical Organization
- Fo, 1914-1936 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  routine literary correspondence; lecture appointments and routine
- Fortune Magazine, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Fr, 1908-1935 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  substantial amount of correspondence with Leo J. Frachtenberg, Executive Director of United Palestine Appeal re campaign; other UPA activities and routine matters connected with UPA
- Ga, 1931-1934 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  personal correspondence with Emanuel Gameron and routine
- Ge, 1932-1934 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  letter to editors of Post, Times Star and Cincinnati Inquirer re unemployment insurance 13111 and routine
- Gh (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Gi, 1906-1935 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  personal correspondence, correspondence with Charlotte Perkins Gilman (1910-16) re working mothers
- Ginsburg, Anna, 1925-1926 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  personal family correspondence
- Gl, 1914-1933 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  correspondence with John M. Glenn, General Director, Russell Sage Foundation re Rubinow's article "Index of Dependency": letter from Harry Glucksman, Executive Director, Jewish Welfare Board congratulating Rubinow on his election to Executive Director of the Brooklyn Federation (1927)
- Glassberg, Benjamin, 1931-1936 (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
  substantial amount of correspondence with B. Glassberg, Superintendent, Department of Out-Door Relief, Milwaukee County, re literary, personal, Lundeen Bill, Wagner-Lewis Bill, conferences, unemployment relief systems; Jewish issues - Hillquit-Thomas controversy (1932)-Socialist convention
- Gluck, Elsie - Education Director, NY Women's Trade Union League, 1933-1935 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  re personal and literary correspondence
- Glucksman, Harry L. - Executive Director, Jewish Welfare Board, 1931-1935 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  re Rubinow becoming member of editorial board of the Jewish Social Service Quarterly and routine
- Go, 1925-1935 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  personal, routine; correspondence with Judge I.M. Golden re Anti-Defamation League and the German situation
- Goldsmith, Samuel A. - Executive Director, Jewish Charities of Chicago, 1926-1936 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  re Jewish immigration; literary; reading of paper at conference of National Conference of Social Work; (1928)-Executive Director, Bureau of Jewish Social Research correspondence re Rubinow's position as editor of the Quarterly
- Golub, J.S. - Director, Bureau of Jewish Education, 1931-1936 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  correspondence re socialized medicine and routine
- Gr, 1914-1936 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  literary correspondence; correspondence with Dr. Herman A. Gray re unemployment insurance pooling; correspondence with Louis B. Greenberg re recommendations for graduate school] in social work
- Gu, 1930-1935 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  personal correspondence
- Ha (Box 4, Folder 17)
  routine literary correspondence; personal, n.d.
- Hacker, Louis M., 1928-1932 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  correspondence re special Census of Jews; literary correspondence; discrimination against the Jews and routine
- Hadassah, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Correspondence with Rose Jacobs re various activities of the organization (budget, reorganization, administration); correspondence with Mrs. Samuel Halprin re general health insurance organization in Palestine
- Hadassah, 1932-1936 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Includes "Newsletter," Nov.-Dec. 1932; correspondence re financial details
- Halsey, Olga S., 1932 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  correspondence re offering her assistance to Ohio Unemployment Commission re her knowledge of British unemployment insurances: plans
- Harper's Magazine, 1926-1933 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  literary correspondence
- Harris, Henry J. - Bureau of Labor, Washington, DC, 1910-1911 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  correspondence re routine correspondence while Rubinow on leave in NY
- He, 1918-1936 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  correspondence with Herrman, Secretary Keven Hayesod, CTD re Mizrachi budget; routine and personal
- Hexter, Maurice B. - Executive Director, Federation Jewish Charities of Boston, 1924-1936 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  correspondence re literary, personal and Palestine (also connected with Jewish Agency for Palestine)
- Hi, 1930-1936 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  personal
- Hillquit, Morris, 1912-1933 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  routine and letters re anti-Semitic tendency in Socialist Party (May 27, June 20, June 27, 1932)
- Himwich, Harold E. - Professor, Yale University, School of Medicine, 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  re personal
- Hirsh, William - Managing Director, Mastbaum Loan System, 1929-1931 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  re personal, literary, unemployment insurance, financial, closing of various banks
- Hirsh, William, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  discusses financial problems, political election re Roosevelt/Hoover/Thomas/Smith; personal and routine
- Hirsh, William, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
  financial and personal, German situation
- Hirsh, William, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Ho, 1923-1934 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Hoehler, F.K. - Director, Department of Public Welfare, Cincinnati, 1929-1935 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  re unemployment insurance for Cincinnati
- Holt & Company, 1923-1935 (Box 4, Folder 36-38)
- Horn, Joseph H. - Northwest Dental Society of the City of NY, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  re Committee on Socio-Economics for Dental Profession (Horn, Chairman of Committee)
- Hourwich, Isaac A., 1931 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  Includes biographical sketch; bibliography and related correspondence used for inclusion in Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences
- Hu, 1926-1934 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  Correspondence re Francis Huyck re Jewish situation in Palestine; and personal and routine
- Hurlin, Ralph G. - Director, Department of Statistics, Russell Sage Foundation, 1926-1928 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  correspondence re Pennsylvania Study of Welfare Statistics and Rubinow serving on Advisory Committee
- Hy, 1925-1935 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  mainly correspondence with Joseph Hyman, Executive Director, Associated Jewish Charities of Baltimore and later Jewish Federation of Indianapolis re speaking engagements for Rubinow and personal
- 11, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Im, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  Immigration Commission, Committee on Immigration Problems, Rubinow as member - correspondence re studies to be undertaken
- In, 1928-1935 (Box 4, Folder 46-47)
  Includes income tax forms and correspondence, routine correspondence; correspondence with Indiana Union of Jewish Youth re Rubinow taking part in their conference
- Intercollegiate Socialist Society, 1914-1918 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  correspondence with Harry W. Laidler, Organizing Secretary re meetings, speakers, articles, etc.
- International Congress on Social Insurance, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  correspondence re Rubinow1s appointment as member of Committee on Organization and routine
- International Health Board, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  correspondence re Rubinow's views on effect of health insurance on public health
- International Union of the United Brewery Workmen, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  correspondence re the unions' compensation plan, requesting Rubinow's views
- Is, 1926-1936 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  re routine and literary correspondence with Edward L. Israel
- Ja, 1926-1936 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  correspondence with Rose Jacobs re Hadassah; literary and routine
- Jacobson, 1929-1935 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  personal and literary correspondence
- Je, 1927-1936 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  literary correspondence, routine
- Jewish Colonization Association, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  re Canadian Jewish statistics, includes 2 manuscripts re Canada's Jews by Louis Rosenberg
- Jewish Frontier, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  literary correspondence with Isidore Abramovitz, Managing Editor; personal
- Jewish National Fund of America, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  personal correspondence re purchase of land
- Jewish Social Service Quarterly, 1927-1936 (Box 4, Folder 59-61)
- Jewish Tribune, 1926-1928 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  correspondence re tribute to Justice Louis D. Brandeis, lengthy description of Brandeis' trip to Palestine by Rubinow
- Jewish Welfare Society, 1923-1935 (Box 4, Folder 63-64)
  re Rubinow's selection as Director of the Society and letters of congratulations; correspondence re Society activities, reports
- Jo, 1926-1935 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  literary correspondence with Alvin Johnson, Assistant Editor, Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences and other routine correspondence
- Joint Committee on Unemployment, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  correspondence re Rubinow as a witness on the Costigan LaFollette Relief Bill; re activities of the Unemployment Committee; manuscript entitled "An Urban Famine, Suffering Communities of Chicago Speak for Themselves;" Summary of open hearings held by the Chicago Workers Committee on Unemployment, Jan. 5-12, 1932
- Journal of Political Economy, 1901-1918 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Ju, 1930-1933 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  personal and routine
- Ka, 1900-1936 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  personal correspondence, financial with Anna Kaplan; correspondence with Arthur Kallet re creation of Consumers' Technical Union; correspondence with Mordecai Kaplan re Hadassah activities
- Kahn, Dorothy - Executive Director, Jewish Welfare Society, 1924-1929 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  correspondent-e re Rubinow1s Secretary and replacing Rubinow as Executive Director of Jewish Welfare Society and Rubinow assisting her in the transition
- Karpf, Maurice J. - Director, Training School for Jewish Social Work, 1927-1935 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  correspondence re advancement for employee of Rubinow's that graduated from School for Jewish Social Work; Lundeen Bill; plans for conference of National Conference of Jewish Social Service
- Katznelson, B. - Assistant Director, Hadasnah Medical Organization, 1923-1929 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  re financial situation of Hadassah; selection of a director; monthly budgets
- Kaznelson, Reuben - Acting Director, Hadassah Medical Organization, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  re his loss of job because of lack of funds; private practice for physicians in Palestine
- Ke, 1919-1936 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  personal and routine correspondence
- Keller, D.C., 1935 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Kelley, Florence - General Secretary, National Consumer's League, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  correspondence re Rubinow's article on sickness insurance
- Kentucky, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  correspondence with Robert Caldwell, Chairman, Eastern District, Workmen's Compensation Board, Frankfort, re insurance rates for compensation
- Ki, 1897-1936 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  personal, literary, lecturing schedules
- Kiefer, Horace S., 1935 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  correspondence re unemployment insurance in Ohio
- Kirsh, Bess - Secretary to Rubinow, 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  correspondence re Kirsh going to New York from Philadelphia to work for Rubinow, leaving Jewish Welfare Society and problems arising from it
- Kittner, Violet - Director Jewish Social Service Bureau, 1931-1936 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  re setting up program for National Conference and various meetings
- Kl, 1927-1935 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Kn, 1932-1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  personal, literary
- Ko, 1919-1935 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  correspondence with Lucien Koch, Director Commonwealth College re financial report for 1933 (Rubinow, member of Advisory Committee); personal; Edwin Kopf, Metropolitan Life Insurance re Rubinow1s Dependency Index article; H. Kobbe, Rand School of Social Science re moving School to another location, suggests Hillquit is a lunatic
- Kohs, S.C., 1931-1936 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Kopf, Edwin W. - Assistant Statistician, Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  re literary and routine
- Kotinsky, Ruth - National Council of Parent Education, 1930-1936 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  personal and literary
- Kr, 1925-1933 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  personal family correspondence and routine
- Ku, 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  correspondence with Sidney G. Kusworm, Independent Order of B'nai B'rith, Executive Director of Americanization re personal and routine
- Ky - with Hazel Kyrk, University of Chicago, Home Economics Department, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  re social legislation for domestic employment
- La-Lap - correspondence with Senator Robert M. LaFollette, Jr., 1907-1936 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  re social security legislation, unemployment relief hearings, personal and routine
- Labor College of Philadelphia, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  re participating in conference
- Lambert, Alexander - Chairman, Judicial Council, American Medical Association, 1915-1917 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  literary and medical profession insurance
- Las-Laz - with Bruno Lasker, 1924-1935 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  re solution to social problems and YMCA in Jerusalem being used by Christians and non-Christians; correspondence with F.E. Latta re poverty and old age; literary correspondence; Pennsylvania legislation re socialized medicine; correspondence with Fred Lazarus re Ohio unemployment insurance
- Lea-Lei - League for Industrial Democracy (Harry Laidler), 1929-1935 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  re participation in program and Rubinow speaking on "socialism"; correspondence with William B Leaf re Rubinow's problems as Executive Director of ZOA (1929); correspondence with Herbert H. Lehman, Lt. Governor, NYS re passage of unemployment insurance bill (1935)
- Lea-Lei, 1916-1936 (Box 5, Folder 28cont.)
  correspondence with William M. Leiserson re Scott Nearing's problems at Toledo University and routine
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1929-1936 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  Correspondence with Harry Laidler and Executive Secretary Mary Fox and Norman Thomas; includes routine re activities of the organization, budgetary problems; speaking engagements
- League for Labor Palestine, 1934-1936 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  re conference in Baltimore and routine
- Lecture Tour, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  letter offering Rubinow services as lecturer on social insurance
- Len-Lev, 1930-1936 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  correspondence with Oscar Leonard re employment opportunities, etc.; personal
- Levy, Jerome, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Lew-Lex, 1918-1935 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Li - letter to J.F. Lincoln, President Lincoln Electric Company, 1911-1936 (Box 5, Folder 35-36)
  re Lincoln's address referring to Rubinow background; correspondence re arrangements for speaking engagements; correspondence with Alice Liveright re her appointment as Commissioner of Welfare Department, Pennsylvania; unemployment insurance Ohio; correspondence with Samuel Lindsay, Director NYC School of Philanthropy re course Rubinow taught on social insurance; and personal
- Liberty Mutual Insurance Company, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  re Company requesting information on law differential for the Federal Workmen's Compensation Act
- Lieberman, Albert, 1927-1936 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  correspondence re various aspects of their careers, mostly routine and personal
- Lo - Louisville, KY; Solomon Lowenstein, Executive Director of Federal for the Support of Jewish Philanthropic Societies of NYC, 1918-1936 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Lorwin, Lewis L. - Chairman, National Economic and Social Planning Association, 1931-1935 (Box 5, Folder 40)